RICHARD ELMLINGER

243 Evane Drive Depew, NY 14043 richelliot243@outlook.com (716) 290-3818

OBJECTIVE

Highly experienced Customer Service and Sales professional. Successful in several high-volume situations in multiple marketplaces. Pursuing an aggressive, growing company which can best utilized my experience.

EXPERIENCE

01/1995-07/2018

Director Customer Service • Tuxedo Junction Inc. • Williamsville, NY Start in B2B sales. Promoted to Call Center manager and then to Director. Involved in all aspects of company.

07/1988–11/1994
Sales Manager • Heidie's Tuxedos • Buffalo, NY
B2B sales and service. Asst. Manager in Home office retail store and production warehouse.

03/1986– 07/1988 District Sales Manager • Van Heusen • Woodbridge, VARICHARD ELMLINGER

SUMMARY

Commissioned sales, Outside B2B sales and service. Sales manager for single and multiple store locations. Supervised Call center inbound and outbound cold call sales. Duties have included collections, recruiting and training, Point person for escalated conflict resolutions.

Acheivements

At Van Heusen managed highest volume district in company. Promoted to DSM after three months. While at Heidie's tuxedos increased wholesale division by 30% in first eighteen months. Long career at Tuxedo Junction, implemented loss prevention methods that reduced company rental loss by 90%. Received company's

highest service award after two years. Help implement diversity work program with Catholic charities for production workforce.

Education

Villa Maria College- AAS degree in Business

REFERENCES

Mike Bristol

President (retired) Tuxedo Junction Inc. (716) 725-3330 / <u>bristolm@gmail.com</u>

Cal Cleveland President (retired) Tuxedo Junction Inc. (716) 725-3283 / calandnancy188@gmail.com